Guide to the Abe Burrows collection of sound recordings [sound recording]
The New York Public Library. Rodgers and Hammerstein Archives of Recorded Sound.
- Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., 1947-48; 915892
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., February 28, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915926; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Khachaturian's "Saber dance" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5628, *LJ-12 5629.; Contents: You ate up a hunk of my heart / Abe Burrows -- Gaiane. Tanets s sabliami / Aram Ilich Khachaturian -- Jose Simba / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Khachaturian, Aram Ilich, 1903-1978; Milton DeLugg Quartet; You ate up a hunk of my heart; Gaiane. Tanets s sabliami; Jose Simba
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., March 6, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915927; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5630, *LJ-12 5631.; Contents: Help, police / Abe Burrows -- Wings over Mars / Milton DeLugg -- Boulder Dam / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Help, police; Wings over Mars; Boulder Dam
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., March 13, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915928; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Dickey bird song" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5632, *LJ-12 5633.; Contents: I'm just sick / Abe Burrows -- Dickey bird song -- Pansy in my garden / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; I'm just sick; Pansy In My Garden; Dickey bird song
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., March 20, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915929; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Cumana" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5634, *LJ-12 5635.; Contents: Give me a man who's a man / Abe Burrows -- Cumana -- Hello springtime / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Give me a man who's a man; Hello springtime; Cumana
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., March 27, 1948; *LTC 9186; 915930; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Bye, bye, blackbird" arranged by DeLugg for the Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LTC 5637, *LJ-12 5636.; Contents: If I was head of the Academy / Abe Burrows -- Bye, bye, blackbird -- Girl in the Easter parade / Abe Burrows -- Love / Abe Burrows -- Englishman / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; If I was head of the Academy; Girl in the Easter parade; Love; Englishman; Bye, bye, blackbird
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., April 3, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915931; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Broadcast from San Francisco. "The Continental" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5590, *LJ-12 5591.; Contents: Hula maiden / Abe Burrows -- Continental -- That train's goin' south / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Hula maiden; That train's goin' south; Continental
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., April 10, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915932; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5592, *LJ-12 5593.; Contents: Bela Lugosi / Abe Burrows -- Don't you love me anymore / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Bela Lugosi; Don't you love me anymore
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., April 17, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915933; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Mary Lou" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5594, *LJ-12 5595.; Contents: Uggle, muggle / Abe Burrows -- Mary Lou -- My heart / Abe Burrows -- Open road / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Uggle, muggle; My Heart; Open Road; Mary Lou
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., April 24, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915934; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "London bridge" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5596, *LJ-12 5597.; Contents: Mr. Moon / Abe Burrows -- London Bridge is falling down -- Brooklyn / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Mr. Moon; Brooklyn; London Bridge is falling down
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., May 1, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915935; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Oye negra" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5598, *LJ-12 5599.; Contents: Effie / Abe Burrows -- Oye negra -- Los Angeles / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Effie; Los Angeles; Oye negra
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., May 8, 1948; *LTC 9187; 915936; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Missouri Waltz" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5600, *LJ-12 5601.; Contents: Gypsy's violin / Abe Burrows -- Missouri waltz -- Vote for me / Abe Burrows -- After / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Gypsy's Violin; Vote for me; After; Missouri Waltz
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., May 15, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915937; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Carioca" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5578, *LJ-12 5579.; Contents: My girl is crazy 'bout me / Abe Burrows -- Carioca -- Maytime / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; My girl is crazy 'bout me; Maytime; Carioca
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., May 22, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915938; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Baby face" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5580, *LJ-12 5581.; Contents: Sweet memories / Abe Burrows -- Baby face -- Purple phantom / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Sweet Memories; Purple phantom; Baby Face
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., May 29, 1948; *LTC 9188; *LTC 9198; 915939; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Bim bam boom" arranged by DeLugg. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 9779. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5582, *LJ-12 5583.; Contents: Baby / Abe Burrows -- Bim bam boom -- Hello type song / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Baby; Hello type song; Bim bam boom
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., June 5, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915940; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Dizzy fingers" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5584, *LJ-12 5585.; Contents: This must be love / Abe Burrows -- Dizzy Fingers.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; This Must Be Love; Dizzy Fingers
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., June 12, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915941; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Mary Jane Croft and Hans Conried join Abe Burrows in performing his "operetta." Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5586, *LJ-12 5587.; Contents: Duke of Dittendorten / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Croft, Mary Jane; Conried, Hans; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Duke of Dittendorten
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., June 19, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915942; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. Broadcast from New York City. "Dolores" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5563, *LJ-12 5564, *LJ-12 5588, *LJ-12 5589.; Contents: Rain / Abe Burrows -- Dolores -- John C. Shulzenhammer High / Abe Burrows -- Upper Peabody / Abe Burrows.; 4 sound discs: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Rain; John C. Shulzenhammer High; Upper Peabody; Dolores
  - Abe Burrows Show (Radio program),., June 26, 1948; *LTC 9188; 915943; Milton DeLugg, accordian, with the Milton DeLugg Quartet. "Oye negra" arranged by DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5553, *LJ-12 5554.; Contents: All of me / Abe Burrows -- Oye negra -- Keep singing / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Milton DeLugg Quartet; All of Me; Keep Singing; Girl with the three blue eyes; Oye negra
- Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., 1949; 915944
  Abe Burrows' second show, which despite its name, aired at night. ("He got up late.")
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., July 4, 1949; *LTC 9178; 915945; Guest: Binnie Barnes. Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Lyn Duddy and the Lyn Duddy Singers; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9777.
    Barnes, Binnie, 1905-; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Duddy, Lyn; Mirandy, Dora; Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Lyn Duddy Singers
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., July 18, 1949; *LTC 9178; 915946; Guest: Hildegarde. Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Lyn Duddy and the Lyn Duddy Singers; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9776.
    Hildegarde, 1906-; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Duddy, Lyn; Mirandy, Dora; Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Lyn Duddy Singers
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., September 16, 1949; *LTC 9179; 915947; Guest: Eddie Cantor. Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9776.
    Cantor, Eddie, 1892-1964; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Mirandy, Dora; Milton DeLugg Orchestra
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., September 23, 1949; *LTC 9179; 915948; Guest: Ethel Merman. Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn) Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9774.
    Merman, Ethel; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Mirandy, Dora; Milton DeLugg Orchestra
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., September 30, 1949; *LTC 9177; 915949; Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Toni Arden, singer; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Guest: Phil Foster. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9774.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Mirandy, Dora; Foster, Phil; Arden, Toni; Milton DeLugg Orchestra
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., October 14, 1949; *LTC 9177; 915950; Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Toni Arden, singer; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9775.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Mirandy, Dora; Arden, Toni; Milton DeLugg Orchestra
  - Breakfast with Burrows (Radio program),., October 28, 1949; *LTC 9176; 915951; Guest: Charlie Cantor. Milton DeLugg and the Milton DeLugg Orchestra; Toni Arden, singer; Dora Mirandy (Marilyn). Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9775.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Cantor, Charles, 1889-1966; DeLugg, Milton; Mirandy, Dora; Arden, Toni; Milton DeLugg Orchestra
- Other radio shows., 915952
  Burrows performs or is a guest on many of these shows.
  Alphabetically by title of radio show.
  - Bing Crosby Show (Radio program),., January 26, 1949; *LTC 9189; 915953; Bing Crosby, host; Abe Burrows, guest, with Peggy Lee. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5575, *LJ-12 5576, *LJ-12 5577.; Contents: I'm just sick / Abe Burrows -- Purple phantom / Abe Burrows.; 3 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Crosby, Bing, 1904-1977; Lee, Peggy; I'm just sick; Purple phantom
  - Bing Crosby Show (Radio program),., February 23, 1949; *LTC 9190; 915954; Abe Burrows is a guest on Crosby's show with Peggy Lee. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5572, *LJ-12 5573, *LJ-12 5574.; Contents: Sweet memories / Abe Burrows -- Duke of Dittendorten / Abe Burrows.; 3 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Crosby, Bing, 1904-1977; Lee, Peggy; Sweet Memories; Duke of Dittendorten
  - Bing Crosby Show (Radio program),., April 27, 1949; *LTC 9190; 915955; Abe Burrows is a guest on Crosby's show, with Peggy Lee and Milton DeLugg. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5569, *LJ-12 5570, *LJ-12 5571.; Contents: Upper Peabody / Abe Burrows -- John C. Shulzenhammer High / Abe Burrows.; 3 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Crosby, Bing, 1904-1977; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Lee, Peggy; DeLugg, Milton; Upper Peabody; John C. Shulzenhammer High
  - Chase Hotel show (Radio program),., March 12, 1949; *LTC 9190; 915956; Excerpts with Abe Burrows, Peter Lind Hayes and Mary Healy. Broadcast from St. Louis. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5705, *LJ-12 5706, *LJ-12 5707.; Contents: Effie / Abe Burrows -- In the back of a hack / Jay Gorney -- Annie get your gun. They say it's wonderful / Irving Berlin.; 3 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Hayes, Peter Lynde; Healy, Mary; Gorney, Jay; Berlin, Irving, 1888-; Effie; In the back of a hack; Annie get your gun. They say it's wonderful
  - Command Performance. (Radio program),., July 8, 1947; *LTC 9189; 915957; Groucho Marx, host; Abe Burrows, guest. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5676.; Contents: Memory lane / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows.; 1 sound disc: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Marx, Groucho, 1891-1977; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Memory Lane; Girl with the three blue eyes
  - Eleanor Roosevelt program,., December 27, 1950; *LTC 9199; 915958; NBC radio broadcast. Abe Burrows, guest. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9773.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Roosevelt, Eleanor
  - Electric hour (Radio program),., August 31, 1947; *LTC 9189; 915959; Woody Herman and Peggy Lee, hosts,; Abe Burrows, guest. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5679.; Contents: Rock and the rose / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows.; 1 sound disc: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Lee, Peggy; Herman, Woody; Rock and The Rose; Girl with the three blue eyes
  - Henry Morgan show (Radio program),., September 10, 1947; *LDC 42526, tracks 13-16; 915960; For William Morris Agency. Abe Burrows spot. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5701; Contents: Tokyo Rose / Abe Burrows -- Pansy in my garden / Abe Burrows.; 1 sound disc: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Morgan, Henry, 1915-; Tokyo Rose; Pansy In My Garden
  - Herb Shriner Show (Radio program),., November 10, 1948; *LTC 9197; 915961; Herb Shriner, with the Raymond Scott Quintet; Abe Burrows, guest. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9777.
    Shriner, Herb, 1918-1970; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Scott, Raymond; Raymond Scott Quintet
  - Jack Smith show (Radio program),., May 19, 1948; *LTC 9189; 915962; Jack Smith, host; Abe Burrows, guest. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5704.; Contents: Sea chanty / Abe Burrows.; 1 sound disc: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Smith, Jack, 1918?-; Sea Chanty
  - Joan Davis Show (Radio program)., *LDC 42531, tracks 7-8; 915963; "After-show" Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5546, *LJ-12 5547 Preservation copy in: *LT-10-A 3311; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Davis, Joan
  - Joan Davis Show (Radio program)., *LJ-12 5548; *LJ-12 5549; 915964; "After-Show" Access restricted. Advanced notification required for use.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Davis, Joan; Burrows, Abe, 1910-
  - Joan Davis Show (Radio program),., May 1947; *LTC 9189; 915965; "Joan Davis preview - not broadcast." Questionable date. Abe Burrows, guest.; Contents: Memory lane / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows -- Waukeshaw natural bridge / Abe Burrows.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Davis, Joan; Memory Lane; Girl with the three blue eyes; Waukeshaw Natural Bridge
  - Joan Davis Show (Radio program),., May 16, 1947; *LTC 9197; 915966; Excerpts: parts 2 & 4 of 4. Performers: Joan Davis, Phil Silvers, Abe Burrows, Delta Rhythm Boys. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9777.
    Davis, Joan; Silvers, Phil, 1911-; Burrows, Abe, 1910-; The Delta Rhythm Boys
  - Let yourself go (Radio program),., November 4, 1948; *LTC 9189; 915967; Abe Burrows, guest. Mostly talk. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5558, *LJ-12 5559.; Contents: Tokyo Rose / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Tokyo Rose
  - Mirth for moderns (Radio program),., December 22, 1949; *LTC 9190; 915968; Abe Burrows, host, with Milton DeLugg, accordian, the Milton DeLugg Quartet and C.C. Blake. Broadcast as part of Voice of the Army, Dec. 22, 1949, 5-6 PM. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5684, *LJ-12 5685.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; Blake, C. C; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Voice of the Army (Radio program)
  - On the Century (Radio program),., 1947; *LTC 9189; 915969; Bob Elson, host, interviews Abe Burrows. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-10 1775.; 1 sound disc: analog, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 10 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Elson, Bob
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., February 1, 1946; *LTC 9172; 915970; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9782.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., February 8, 1946; *LTC 9172; 915971; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9782.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., February 22, 1946; *LTC 9173; 915972; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9780.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., March 2, 1946; *LTC 9173; 915973; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9780.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., March 8, 1946; *LTC 9174; 915974; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9781.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., March 15, 1946; *LTC 9174; 915975; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9781.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., March 29, 1946; *LTC 9175; 915976; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9778.
  - Philip Morris Holiday Show (Radio program),., April 12, 1946; *LTC 9175; 915977; Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9778.
  - Stars for defense (Radio program),., December 6, 1957; *LTC 9190; 915978; Abe Burrows with Milton DeLugg. Program no. 67. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5700.; Contents: I'm just sick / Abe Burrows -- A / Abe Burrows -- Lopin' along / Abe Burrows -- Girl with the three blue eyes / Abe Burrows.; 1 sound disc: analog, 33 1/3 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; DeLugg, Milton; I'm just sick; A; Lopin' Along; Girl with the three blue eyes
  - Treasury bandstand (Radio program)., *LDC 28828; 915979; Jimmy Boyd, singer; Ray Sinatra, conductor. Track listing on file. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 12368. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-7-A 1475.; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips, acetate-based; 7 in.
    Boyd, Jimmy; Sinatra, Ray
  - Two for the show (Radio program),., January 7, 1948; *LTC 9189; 915980; Abe Burrows, guest, with Lyndell Barbour. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5556, *LJ-12 5557.; Contents: I'm not sick of you / Abe Burrows -- Rock and the rose / Abe Burrows.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Barbour, Lyndall; I'm not sick of you; Rock and The Rose
  - Voice of the Army (Radio program)., *LTC 9199; 915981; Program no. 442 "Abe Burrows Show". Sponsored by the U.S. Army and Air Force. Milton DeLugg Quartet, directed by Major Hugh K. Murray. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 9773. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5674, *LJ-12 5675.; 2 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate, mono.; 12 in.
    Burrows, Abe, 1910-; Murray, Hugh K; Milton DeLugg Quartet; Abe Burrows show (Radio program)
  - Voice of the Army (Radio program)., *LTC 9199; 915982; Program no. 441 "I can hear it now" with Edward R. Murrow. Murrow hosts a program of important news highlights cought on radio from 1933-1945. Sponsored by the U.S. Army & Air Force. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-10 9773.
    Murrow, Edward R; I can hear it now (Radio program)
  - We take your word (Radio program),., January 26, 1951; *LDC 42531, tracks 1-6; 915983; Rerecorded 1/24/51. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LJ-12 5693, *LJ-12 5694, *LJ-12 5695, *LJ-12 5696, *LJ-12 5697 Preservation copy in: *LT-10-A 3311; 5 sound discs: analog, 78 rpm, aluminum-based acetate; 12 in.
- Television program appearances., 915984
  Audio portion only.
  Alphabetically by title of show.
  - At the movies (Television program)., *LDC 27372; 915985; TV special with Sid Caesar, Audrey Meadows and Art Carney. Sponsored by Rexall. Track listing for CD service copy on file. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 12317. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-7-A 1477.; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips, acetate-based, mono.; 7 in.
    Caesar, Sid, 1922-; Meadows, Audrey; Carney, Art
  - Dinah Shore Show (Television program),., 1959; *LDC 27371; 915986; Brief excerpt. Track listing for CD service copy on file. Preservation copy in: *LT-10 12317. Access to original items restricted. Original in: *LT-7-A 1477.; 1 sound tape reel: analog, 1 7/8 ips, acetate-based, mono.; 7 in.